(Raj:)And you know what will be on
that elephant's back? A seat warmer.
"No, Father, you may not have a ride!"
(Bernadette:)I'm gonna make some coffee.
So who do you schmooze
to get this deal?
(Leonard:)I'm not gonna schmooze anybody.
I'm gonna let my work speak for itself.
- That's great. That shows a lot of integrity.
- Thank you.
(Leonard:)I'm a naive idiot, right?
(Penny:)Oh, good, you heard me.
(Amy:)If you really want tenure,
cozy up to the people making the decision.
(Sheldon:)Sheldon Cooper does not do cozy.
(Amy:)You don't say.
(Sheldon:)But I suppose it wouldn't hurt
to know who's on the committee.
Let's see. Janine Davis. Oh, dear.
- Is that a problem?
- Well...
(Sheldon:)Even you. You're a slave.